SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
- Cheers.
From now on, I want nails like Lumi's.
Sharp nails.
If someone bullies me,
- I'll scratch them.
- Scratch them!
- Scratch them.
- Yes.
I'll raise my glass.
Today, not only did I defeat
the scummy agency,
but I also fired my boss.
Stupid boss. I don't
have to put up with him anymore.
- Congratulations to me.
- Congratulations to you.
Congratulations!
That saying
by what's-his-name is so right.
"You hold the sail of your future."
I've decided that tomorrow,
I'll start my own business.
You don't find flatmates
who fight with you in Beijing every day.
I am a lucky girl.
Don't laugh at me, but at work,
I keep getting the short end of the stick,
but when I see the three of you
at home, all my misery disappears.
It doesn't affect me anymore.
- What's the big deal?
- Yeah. What's the big deal?
Even if the four of us
don't live together anymore,
- our bond will not break.
- It won't.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Just what have we done this year?
And we end the year with bruises.
It's a crazy ending to a year well spent.
We have experienced
both the good and the bad.
- We deserve a celebration.
- Yes, we do.
- Cheers.
That day, we drank a lot.
The boys puked everywhere.
Life forces us to be invincible.
But everything will come to an end.
People come and go.
TWO PERSONS, ONE HEART
Come. Let me pet you. Let me pet you.
Good boy.
Shang Zhitao.
This is your new flatmate?
He's not staying at my home.
Take him away.
Luan Nian, are you afraid of dogs?
But I promised the pet store owner
that I'd take him away today.
He stinks.
No, he doesn't.
No, you don't.
- What's his name?
- What?
What is your stupid dog's name?
He's…
His name is Dog.
A stupid name by a stupid person.
Once we're home, he'll stay
in the garage or on the balcony.
No.
He stays where I live.
Or I'll move to the balcony or the garage.
He can move in,
but make sure he stays away from me.
Don't worry. He's an introvert.
He won't approach you.
Good boy.
Verified. Please open the door.
Go.
You never use the bags I bought you.
I can't bring myself to open them.
Maybe in the future.
In the future, I'll use them.
Move.
Introvert, you say?
Can't you read his face?
Can't you see if someone likes
or hates you?
Don't just approach anyone.
He doesn't like you. Understood?
He will not step on my rug.
I'm warning you. Stay away from me.
If you piss me off, I'll hit you.
Don't go there. Come.
Luke. Come here.
Luke, don't move.
Come here. Quick.
Who are you calling?
What did you just call him?
I called him…
Dog.
What is his true name?
Luke.
This stupid pet of yours is called Luke?
- Luan Nian!
- Go away.
- Luan Nian.
- Get out.
Get out.
I named him Luke
because that was the first thing
that came into my mind.
And I think it's a great name.
It rolls off your tongue.
And I hope Luke
can keep me company every day.
You can't call him Luke.
Fine. I'll change the name.
I'll call him
Alex.
What do you think? Alex is not bad.
Whatever. I don't care.
Luke it is, then.
Come, Luke.
Say hello to Uncle Luan. Uncle Luan.
Uncle Luan.
He calls you sister, but calls me uncle?
How does that make sense?
Just look at him. Touch him.
Touch him, please. He's so cute.
Touch him.
Luke.
Look how blank-faced he is.
Don't stare at me. I'm talking about you.
Ignore him.
Silly dog who sheds.
Useless.
All right, Luke. Go play over there.
All right. Luke, go play over there.
Don't yell at him.
You look so scary. Don't be like that.
Don't.
Hug. Hugs.
Luke is so sweet. Don't be mean to him.
Luke.
Shang Zhitao.
Take your stupid dog
and get out of my room.
Okay. Luke.
Then I'll sleep with him
in the guest room.
I have to wake up early tomorrow anyway.
It's the weekend.
Why do you need to wake up early?
I have a French class.
And I need to check out
new apartments with my flatmates.
Do you go on a date
with that foreigner every weekend?
It's a tuition class.
Come, Luke.
Luke.
Goodnight, Luke.
A tuition class?
Okay.
J'ai hâte…
…de collaborer…
…avec vous.
J'ai hâte de collaborer avec vous.
I look forward to working with you.
C'est génial.
Great. You learn faster than I do.
Merci.
Hello, Sun Yu.
Hey, Tao.
I'll be done soon.
Which apartment are we viewing today?
No need for that anymore.
The housing is sorted out.
We don't need to move anymore.
- Lei, you tell her.
- Who?
- Tao.
- Tao. Tao.
My friends lent me some money.
I bought back my ex-wife's property.
You don't need to find another home.
Just come home.
We can all go home
and celebrate Chinese New Year.
You hear that? Come home.
That's great! Long Zhentian.
I don't have to move away.
We don't have to be apart.
- C'est la vie.
That's great!
Again.
- J'ai hâte
de collaborer…
I'm back.
You're back.
- So many things.
- You're back, Tao.
Yes.
- We're unpacking.
- Where do I put this?
- Lei.
- Tao, you're back.
I didn't know we had
this many things until we had to move out.
Now that all of us are here,
allow me to say "Welcome Home."
One more thing.
This will be our home, now and forever.
Yeah!
This is wonderful.
There's nothing like home.
I was thinking of getting
a longer dining table.
That way, we can work at the same place.
Good.
We can redesign
the layout of the living room
and replace the sofa and the bookshelf.
I want to put two plant stands here.
I'll buy some plants and flowers.
And get a fishbowl. To bring in fortune.
- We'll raise the fish together.
- I also want a pet.
What kind of pet?
I want a dog.
A dog?
Lei, are you afraid of dogs?
- No way.
- Great.
- Yuanzhu?
- I'm fine with dogs.
Really?
It's unanimous then.
The Samoyed will be
the fifth member of this house.
Field member?
Fifth member.
I heard field member. Come. Get to work.
Stop messing around.
My back is killing me.
Start unpacking now. Stop talking.
- I'll take care of the window.
- Okay.
Careful, Lei.
I'm fine.
Where do I hang this?
Here.
There's a nail here.
Tao, check if it's centered.
It's centered.
Lei, can you carry the sofa with me?
Sure.
It's my third year in Beijing.
I'm so incredibly lucky
to have moved into this unit.
My flatmates in 301
are my family in Beijing.
For the first time in my life,
this city feels like home.
BE HAPPY TODAY
It's a weekend flight.
My annual leave
can last till the end of February.
Wait.
I hear a girl singing.
Is that your girlfriend?
I don't want to discuss this.
I don't intend to bring her home.
Is it because you're worried
your dad will give her a hard time?
Don't worry. I'll talk to him.
It's not yet the right time.
All right. I'll let you decide.
I'll hang up now.
Sorry. I didn't know
you were having a phone call.
- I didn't mean to sing out loud.
- You're very happy today.
My flatmates told me
we got the house back.
I'll move back soon.
Thank you for letting me
crash at your place.
How much is your rent?
Around 1,000 yuan.
Rent a room with me.
I'll charge you 500 yuan.
Thanks,
but I prefer to stay with my flatmates.
We agreed on it.
Are you that reluctant
to leave your flatmates?
They are all very kind.
Congratulations then.
You found good flatmates.
I don't intend to bring her home.
It's not yet the right time.
Thanks, my puppy.
Come. Here.
Why did you come out?
To get some air.
Silly dog.
Come here. Come.
- Luke.
- Your dog is quite strong.
Sit.
Come here.
Lazy dog.
He likes you a lot.
Shang Zhitao.
Let's go to the bar
in the mountains tomorrow.
Okay.
Let's go, silly dog.
Let's go.
- What do you think?
- The renovation is already done?
It looks good.
- Luke.
- Luke, come here.
This is better than I imagined.
Do you like it?
I love your renovation choices.
Let Luke roam freely.
Go, Luke. Don't pee or poop anywhere.
He won't.
Once the glassware is here, you will
have the first drink from the bartender.
When is the bartender coming?
You know how to mix drinks?
When this place opens to the public,
you will be our first client.
And you shall witness my mixing skills.
For the moment,
I can only make you sky juice.
Sky juice? Just call it mineral water.
Luke.
Come and drink.
Come. Luke.
Don't drink this one for the opening day.
My friend gave me a bottle
of 25-year-old whiskey.
Allow me to introduce.
This is Shang Zhitao.
I don't have to introduce myself.
I've already met her.
This is our first meeting.
I am Song Qiuhan.
We are Luke's best friends from school.
Listen. I've known him for many years,
and this is the first time
he has introduced his girlfriend to us.
Come, Ms. Shang.
What an honor.
I finally met you.
- Now that I've met you…
- Are you out of your mind?
Now that I've met you, I see you
not only raise a good dog,
but also do a good job managing Luke.
Are you sick? What are you trying to say?
I'm saying you are obedient.
When it comes to obedience,
no one can outdo a simp like you.
We're the same.
Luke, what made you decide
to open a bar here?
Even if it doesn't make any money,
won't you want to recoup your cost?
Exactly. It's a remote place.
How is it going to be successful?
Speaking of business,
all of you have a share in this bar.
A surprise?
Share Purchase Agreement.
What is the meaning of this?
Does this mean we will be jointly liable
if this business fails?
This bar is not open to the public,
but it's fully booked this week.
The Anns from Fumei Group
and Ruixing Group
will be here for an event
in the next two days.
Next week, the newly appointed
Mr. Guan of Yuanjing will be here.
It's not open to the public,
meaning it's like a private club.
- See?
- It seems like we are too shortsighted.
When it comes to running a bar,
you are much better than Song.
I didn't know
you had such business acumen.
Otherwise, I really should have asked you
to run my bar back then.
Why should I work for you?
Right. You'll be the boss.
- I wouldn't have lost so much money.
- Exactly.
- Come.
- Drink up.
Come.
Allow me to introduce.
This is Shang Zhitao.
I've known him for many years,
and this is the first time
he has introduced his girlfriend to us.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HOSPITALITY
SORRY FOR THE TROUBLE!
HARBIN
LAOLIANGKOU RESTAURANT
Here it is.
Luke, I'll take you to visit relatives
on Chinese New Year's Day.
Coming.
- Wow.
- Two more dishes.
- Hey, my good boy.
- Come.
Have you learned
how to bow with your paws?
If you have, you'll get the red envelopes,
and then, I'll buy meat for you.
Mom, don't feed him meat.
He'll eat kibble.
Meat is too salty.
Luke, Grandpa will light firecrackers
with you later.
Grandpa? Dad, you sure are eager
to be a grandpa.
He's one of our family members.
Come. It's all your favorite.
- Aren't they good?
- They are perfect.
- Dig in.
I'm heading to Suzhou
after Chinese New Year
for more than two months
for my business trip.
- I have to eat more now.
- Come. Dig in.
- You've worked hard, Tao.
- Come. Look.
Come.
Cheers.
Oh.
Last night, Zang Yao came to me.
She was drunk, and she cried a lot.
She said she wanted to let go of you.
Like for real this time.
It'll only do her good.
She said she finally realized
that Shang Zhitao was special to you.
She has never seen you like this before.
I know why you did what you did,
but we grew up with Zang Yao.
You could have been kinder to her.
What? Is giving her
false hopes kindness now?
All right. Stop criticizing Luan Nian.
Luke. Tell us honestly.
Is this a serious relationship or not?
I've never fooled around
with my relationships.
Right.
How come you didn't bring
Ms. Shang home for Chinese New Year?
- It's none of your business.
- Okay.
Happy Chinese New Year.
I wish you well.
May your Luke grow bigger.
Happy Chinese New Year. Cheers.
- Come. Happy Chinese New Year.
- Happy Chinese New Year.
Happy Chinese New Year.
ONE MONTH LATER, SUZHOU
- Just put it here.
- Sure.
Thank you so much.
You and Yuanzhu went on a business trip.
I'll take care of our home. Don't worry.
I'm taking good care of Luke as well.
I knew I could count on you.
Luan Nian will be here soon.
- I'm waiting for him here.
- Okay.
- I will be home soon.
- Flora.
Mr. Wang.
You have worked hard in the past month.
I heard Luke would be here.
- Yes. He…
- Flora.
Morning, Luke.
This is Mr. Wang
from the event management company.
This is our boss, Luke.
You must have had a long journey.
I'll book a private room
to treat you and Flora
- to a meal.
- Sure.
But we can have the meal anytime.
We have a conference soon.
How is the progress?
The setup is almost done.
The guest reception
has been duly arranged.
The rehearsal will begin at 3 p.m.
Go to the venue
and double-check the schedule.
Then, bring your team with you
for a meeting.
I shall wait for you two at the venue.
Let me know if you need me.
I think your creative proposal
does not align
with the client's strategic direction.
What do the people think on your end?
Well, Mr. Luan.
Let me bring you up to speed
regarding our comments.
We are now pushing
for a collaboration with the brand.
We hope to leverage their resources
to increase our visibility.
It's cheap and boosts our visibility.
The client wants us
to expand the target audience
to the younger generation.
- So the idea
- Bring me a bottle of water.
has to be surprising.
Given the current media trend,
we can use videos,
product placements,
or targeted placement in vertical markets.
It's sort of like digital menus.
But we also have a more traditional idea,
which is more aligned
with the brand's direction.
Carry on.
Working with online content,
we have selected five major influencers
on Weibo whose tone matches our brand
and bloggers in vertical fields.
They cover fashion, lifestyle,
tech, and digital products.
As for the frequency,
we allocate three days to build hype,
two days for peak days,
and one week for the long tail period.
We will send you the influencer
fan profiles and audience overlap data
with our target brand audience by tonight.
As for physical events, we have come up
with three interactive segments.
The first one is a flash mob.
The second is a QR code
that unlocks our brand's history.
And the third one is the Weibo mega screen
- Take the meeting minutes.
- that visitors can interact with.
We estimate more
than 3,000 visitors per show.
I see.
I think we can swap the order
of these two proposals.
Okay.
It's around 7 p.m. now.
Let's take a break.
- A 40-minute dinner break.
- Okay.
- We'll continue after the meal.
- Hello. It's the food delivery.
Pardon me.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Did you miss me?
You've been on this business trip
for a long time.
Have you ever missed me?
Is everyone here? Let's begin.
Sure, Mr. Luan. So, we chose
a venue next to Taihu Lake this time.
It fits perfectly with this year's
Traditional Chinese-style initiative,
the localization of international brands,
and the brand's re-invigoration
of traditional culture.
They are trending topics at the moment.
And the latest strategy in Lime China
is to study the local culture
to bring out the Chinese spirit.
Tell me more about the itinerary.
Please confirm
the subsequent marketing plans
- with me today as well.
- I will send the itinerary to you soon.
As for the marketing plans,
we will conduct a survey
with the Creative Division
before finalizing them.
All right. Good work.
That's all for today's meeting.
Sure.
Hello?
The headquarters are planning
to bring in a general manager.
Are you aware of it?
We'll speak later.
I have to go now.
You won't stay here?
No.
I need to check on the progress
and write the work report.
Do you know how to write one?
Do you need my help?
No need.
I don't need your help
to get my promotion.
Thank you for the offer, Mr. Luan.
I'll send you some insider websites later.
Other than working hard,
knowing how to demonstrate
your growth and achievement
is very important at work as well.
Are you actually helping me?
Shang Zhitao.
I hope you'll get the promotion
because you have achieved many things
and have a great working attitude.
Your brain is also better than before.
Is that a compliment?
Didn't you tell me
to compliment you occasionally?
Tao.
You're finally back.
Your business trip was so long.
How was it?
It was okay.
What?
We have a new general manager now.
He's on the same level as Luke.
- What do you mean?
- His name is Dony.
A pretentious elite who returned to China.
Apparently, the board sent him here.
I did my research.
His resume is as impressive as Luke's.
There's a rumor recently saying
that Luan Nian will become
the general manager.
Then, he suddenly appears.
It's fishy.
They don't want Luke
to become too powerful.
They want to keep him in check.
It's not a good thing, I'm sure.
What is your opinion regarding
the investment ratio of the new media?
I think we can study the recent--
Sorry for the interruption.
Allow me to introduce.
This is the new general manager
of the Business Division,
Dony. He will be in charge
of the new media marketing strategy.
Welcome on board.
The headquarters wants him
to join today's meeting.
I'll let you guys work.
Luke. I've heard about you.
I look forward to working with you.
Likewise.
We were talking about next year's
new media marketing proposal.
Join us.
I've read the proposal before I came here.
I think it can use some new ideas.
We are now in the digital era.
Independent media outlets
have become influential.
The interaction between users
and media shouldn't remain unchanged.
We must inject new life into the image
for better user interaction
and retention rate. Don't you agree?
Right.
You want an A/B test.
We at Lime support new strategies
and different perspectives.
I look forward to reading your proposal.
Thank you, Luke.
Let's go over this again.
Sure. Carry on without me.
I have a meeting later, don't I?
And welcome. Familiarize yourself
with our work.
If you have time,
you can take a walk outside too.
Beijing has changed a lot.
You must be Flora.
Dony.
I was told you handled the cases
regarding new media marketing.
I need to relaunch several projects.
Can you help me?
Sure. Let me know if you need me.
I definitely need your assistance.
I'll ask my division to send you
the meeting notification as well.
Do it well. I have plenty of opportunities
for you to shine.
- Okay.
- Go back to your work.
Dony?
Why him of all people?
And parachuted into the office as well?
He's up to no good.
What rotten luck.
Luan Nian has a history with him.
I told you that a guy
betrayed Luan Nian back then.
He was that guy.
They are our rivals.
What did they offer you?
You took my core idea as your ticket in.
I spent three months working on it.
What is the meaning of this?
You can't say it was your effort alone.
I was the one who dealt with the client.
If you don't want to work with me,
you may leave.
The company can be closed down.
But you took my core idea
and sold it to our rivals
to use it against me. Now that's betrayal.
Do you have no shame?
We were brothers.
I do not think I did you wrong.
You know very well this company
has burned through all its cash.
Yes, you are rich,
but I'm not.
I cannot run on an empty stomach
to waste time with you
on your so-called pursuit of perfection.
The priority for this company
is to survive.
You're committing a crime.
I'm seeking legal action.
I really hate that you always
put on that artist act.
You think you're the only genius?
Without me, your unrealistic idea
has no value.
It's just a pipe dream. Do you get it?
Whether it's a pipe dream or not
does not mean
I can't kick you out of this place.
‪WHISPERING PEAKS CREATIVE STUDIO
I didn't want to tell you all this,
but I know you are special to Luke.
As you already know, he is a prideful man.
Even though you now know the story,
do not bring it up in front of him.
Can you mix a drink for me?
A special drink.
What is it called?
It has no name.
No name?
I'll name it then.
Let's call it
One Heart.
What are you getting at?
Lumi told me that Dony
had a complicated background.
Not only did he ask me
to join his new project,
but he also asked several other
key employees to join him.
That's work for you.
Things are not simple.
If someone asks you to pick a side,
will you do it?
Pick his side,
and I might become your enemy.
If you don't, you might be eliminated.
I will never betray you.
And I will never
put my guard up against you.
Oh. I have a business trip in two days.
Can you look after Luke for me?
No. Because I might cook him.
Sure.
Why don't you cook me first?
Cook me first, then cook him next.
You're not delicious
because you lack a brain.
You…
That won't work, Shang Zhitao.
No.
Please.
Take care of him, please?
If he pees in my room, I'll smack him.
If he bites my things, I'll smack him too.
Okay. He needs
to be responsible for his actions.
Smack him.
Do you like it?
I can take three of it
without any problem.
Aren't I amazing? Have I improved myself?
Of everything you can improve on,
you picked drinking?
What if I had to drink at a social event?
I would hold my drinks better than before.
Drinking is never mandatory
at any social event.
Remember what I told you?
Yes.
Turn down drinks if I can.
I don't like it
when you drink with someone else.
Can you do that for me?
Okay.
Pinky promise.
Whoever tells a lie
- will sink to the bad place.
- You're crazy.
NORTHWESTERN CHINA
Hello, Yuanzhu.
I have come to your region!
Luke!
Hongqi has put on some weight.
I feel the atmosphere
at the office has been weird lately.
Everyone has been gossiping.
Focus on your work.
Don't worry about other things.
Don't get yourself involved.
Yes.
Because I'm small and insignificant.
Who am I to worry about everything?
You're small.
But not insignificant.